[{"answer": "What", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Well, who's gonna kiss my sister", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend!!", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Tiger!  Dragon! Iceberg!!  my friend, did you even study at all last night", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "Then do Iceberg", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "What?! I didn't touch a guitar", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No, I'm not questioning it, I'm saying it's stupid!  What?!", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Really?! Uhh, what color is it", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "Well, I'm just'if the paste matches the pants, you can make yourself a pair of paste pants and she won't know the difference", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Oh my God, it's so huge, but you just have to promise me that you cannot tell anyone", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Yes! Yes! Yes, you do want to know! This is unbelievable", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Oh no, n", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "I don't care, Rach! Look, I am tired of being the guy who knows all the secrets but can't tell anyone", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Yes! Yes! Yes, you do want to know! This is unbelievable", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "What? What secrets? You know secrets? What are they", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I don't care, Rach! Look, I am tired of being the guy who knows all the secrets but can't tell anyone", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "And you're not supposed to be gossiping!", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "Do you know something", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Do you know something", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "I might know something", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Do you know something", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "I might know something too", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "I might know something", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "What's the thing you know", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "I might know something too", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Oh no, I can't tell you until you tell me what you know", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "What's the thing you know", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "I can't tell you what I know", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Oh no, I can't tell you until you tell me what you know", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "Well then I can't tell you what I know", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "All right, how about I go over there and I will walk into my friend's bedroom and I will see that thing that I think that I know is actually the thing that I think that I know!", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "AND YOU KNOW!!", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " YOU KNOW!!!", "docId": "511towr.htm.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "Yeah, I know!!!", "qsentId": 36}]